本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： 黑色风车 红鼻子的UFO Cinderella Nick冰 猫
校对： cinderella   后期： 泡面小小
东区女巫前情回顾...
Previously on Witches of East End...
关于她们父亲的事你都说了些什么?
What have you told them about their father?
她们难道没有权利知道他还活着吗?
Don't they have a right to know that he's alive?
可我们永远都不能告诉任何人
We are never, ever going to tell anyone.
你和基利安之间怎么回事?
What happened between you and Killian?
我们接吻了
We kissed.
一个是你的灵魂伴侣 一个是你的冤家
One man is your soul mate, the other man is your destroyer.
弗雷娅
Freya.
其实我在挖掘一些神秘的信息...
I'm actually looking for something more about the occult...
巫术 咒语 神灵
Witchcraft, curses, spirits.
貌似是由某种骨组织构成的
It appears to be made of some sort of osseous tissue.
在费尔黑文的地下墓穴里有一整面墙的枝毒
There's an entire wall of Ramus Mortium in the catacombs of Fair Haven.
你到底是谁?
Who the hell are you?
谢谢你 弗雷娅...
Thank you, Freya...
- 我的法力消失了 - 什么?
- My powers are gone. - What?
带着身体 精神和灵魂
With body, spirit, and soul,
让这孩子重归完整
this child again becomes whole.
重塑
Restituo.
重生
Nativitas.
重现
Filia.
重塑
Restituo.
重生
Nativitas.
重现
Filia.
不起作用
It didn't work.
也许这个咒语我们根本破不了
Maybe this isn't a spell we can break.
弗雷娅 你的法力不只是被锁定了
Freya, your powers aren't just blocked.
它们消失了 弗雷娅
They're gone, Freya.
什么 永远都没了?
What, forever?
你们觉得这是假冒者干的吗?
And you think the shifter is the one who took them?
塔罗牌显示假冒者的法力不足以直接袭击我们
The tarot said the shifter wasn't powerful enough to come at us directly.
但如果假冒者吸走了弗雷娅的法力
But if the shifter has taken Freya's powers,
那就不一样了
everything has changed.
- 他们会强大得多 - 会有多强?
- They're getting stronger. - How strong?
- 和我们一样 - 甚至会更强
- As strong as we are. - If not more.
拜托你告诉我这戏剧性效果是你弄出来的
Please tell me you did that for dramatic effect.
事情越来越严重了
Things are getting serious.
别担心 女士们 就要结束了
Don't worry, ladies, it's almost over.
东区女巫 第一季第09集
发生什么事了
What's happening?
我们发现了个咒语
Oh, we found a spell.
能恢复我的法力?
To get my powers back?
不能 但它能帮我们找到假冒者是谁
No, but it'll help us work out who the shifter is.
- 怎么做? - 每当一个女巫施咒时
- How? - Every time a witch casts a spell,
都会留下一个记号 就像是魔法指纹
it leaves a kind of signature, like a magic fingerprint.
这又是什么意思?
Oh, what does that mean?
你可以把它想成DNA式的证据
Just think of it as DNA evidence.
没错 也许还能从你的血液里追踪到
Exactly, so the shifter's fingerprint may still be traceable
假冒者的指纹
in your blood,
我们会把它提取出来
so we're gonna try and draw it out.
- 把手给我 - 哦...
- Give me your hand. - Oh...
- 哎呦! - 可能会有点儿疼
- Oh! - This may hurt a little.
哎哟! 老天... 哪止一点儿疼?
Ow! Oh, my G... a little?
天哪
Ow, oh, my God.
好了 这些够了
All right, that's enough.
天哪
Oh, my God.
愈合
Consuo.
老天爷 真怀念我有魔力的日子
God, I really miss being able to do things like that.
我理解 亲爱的
Aw, I know, honey.
好了 再跟我们说一遍 你失去魔法的那天
Okay, one more time, take us through the day you lost them.
不要遗漏任何细节
And don't leave anything out.
好 那时候我正在工作
Okay, so I was at work,
我收到了鲜花 然后就感到怪怪的 很难受
I had flowers delivered to me, and I started to feel strange, really sick,
然后我和佩内洛普回到费尔黑文
and then I went back to Fair Haven with Penelope,
然后我晕过去了 后来达什出现并救了我
and I passed out, and then Dash showed up and saved me.
我知道你也许会觉得那花有问题
I know you think it's the flowers,
但也许是别的东西搞得鬼
but maybe it's something else...
比如佩内洛普啊 达什啊
Penelope, Dash.
什么? 不是吧
What? Come on.
不 我告诉过你 我很早之前就测试过达什
No, I told you, I tested Dash a long time ago.
他是凡身 不是他 佩内洛普也是
He's mortal, it is not him, and the same with Penelope.
不是他们
They're fine.
等等 你测试过达什? 为什么呀?
I'm sorry, you tested Dash? Why?
你们进展得太快了
You guys got engaged so quickly
而且你又经常说起这段神秘的恋情
and you kept talking about this mystical love.
我当然得确定一下他有没有隐瞒自己的真身
I had to be sure he was who he said he was.
他是我的灵魂伴侣 我们是天注定的
He's my soul mate. We are destined.
你不是用塔罗牌算过了吗
Come on, you read my tarot.
塔罗牌说他可能是灵魂伴侣
The tarot said he might be,
但他也有可能是骗子 是你的劫难
but he could also be the trickster, your destroyer.
好吧 不是达什干的 绝对不可能
Okay, Dash did not do this. It is not possible.
我同意
I agree.
好了 我得去工作了
Okay, I have to go to work.
你什么时候测的佩内洛普?
When did you test Penelope?
- 还没呢 - 什么?
- I didn't. - What?
但她今晚要来参加彩排晚宴
But she's coming for the rehearsal dinner tonight.
我们可以趁机测试她以及所有其他客人
We can test her then to be sure and all of the other guests.
行
Yeah.
很遗憾你不来参加婚礼
I'm sorry that you won't be coming to the wedding
和彩排晚宴了
or the rehearsal dinner.
- 我觉得这样比较好 - 非常赞同
- I think it's best. - I couldn't agree more.
达什只是需要点时间
Dash just needs some time.
没关系
That doesn't matter.
我已经放下了 但一来这儿我还是会感到焦虑
I'm past that. I was getting antsy here anyway.
我打算去哥斯达黎加过冬
Going to Costa Rica for the winter.
你知道我在每一个地方都待不久的
You know I can't spend too long in one place.
我们能在婚礼以后再讨论此事吗?
Can't we please discuss this after the wedding?
我已经决定了 妈妈 明天下午我就走
Made up my mind, Mom. I'm going tomorrow afternoon.
我保证这次会写信
I promise to write this time.
- 你知道还有个咒语... - 不行
- You know there is one more spell... - No.
- 你都不知道我要说啥 - 你想说
- You didn't know what I was going to say. - You were going to say
我应该问问维克托
that I should call Victor
看他能不能恢复弗雷娅的法力
to see if he'll get Freya's powers back.
不 我没想说这个...
No, I wasn't...
- 不过你应该试试 - 不可能...
- But you should. - There's no way...
那咒语可能有用 乔
The spell could work, Jo.
也可能没用啊 根本不能保证
And it could not. There's no guarantee.
维克托是个医生 我相信他知道怎样做安全
Victor is a doctor, I'm sure he knows how to do it safely.
抱歉 不值得冒这个险
I'm sorry, it's just not worth taking the risk.
色调有点单一呢
It's a little monochromatic.
这什么意思?
What does it mean?
这是我第一次尝试这个咒语
This is the first time I've ever done this spell,
魔法书里说
but according to the Grimoire,
指纹会慢慢地浮到表面
the fingerprint slowly rises to the surface,
希望我们能找出我们的敌人是谁
and hopefully we'll know who our enemy is.
给你
Here you go.
这就是吗?
Is that it?
你看起来美若天仙
You look unbelievable.
真的吗...?
Really...?
裙子完美 你也完美
It's perfect. You look perfect.
所有事都是完美的
Everything is perfect.
不是每件事都完美
Everything is not perfect.
有个变形人悄悄接近我们偷走了我的法力
There's a shape-shifter moving in on us and I've lost my powers.
妈妈和温迪可以解决变形人的问题
Mom and Wendy will handle the shifter,
我知道这听起来有点儿 额...
and I know this may sound, um...
你有没有觉得失去法力
Have you ever thought that losing your powers
对你来说其实是件好事?
is actually for the best?
额 不觉得
Um, no.
自从你发现了我们的身份
Ever since you found out who you are,
你就备受折磨 因为你必须向达什隐瞒这件事
you've been tortured because you couldn't tell Dash.
而你不想骗他 不是吗?
You hated lying to him, right?
那当然 可是...
Of course, but...
现在你再也不用撒谎了
Now you don't have to lie anymore.
- 你可以完全做你自己 - 不
- You are who you are. - No.
我感觉不对 很空虚
I feel wrong, empty,
就好像我丢了一部分自己一样
like I'm missing a piece of myself.
嘿 这里越来越...
Hey, it's getting pretty...
我在外面等你
I will meet you back out there.
我猜你没有收到周五便装日的备忘
I guess you didn't get the memo about Casual Friday.
我只是试一下
I was just trying it on.
我明天就结婚了 我们把婚礼提前了
I'm getting married tomorrow. We moved up the wedding.
是啊 我知道 我听说了
Yeah, I know, I heard.
我知道我应该跟你说一声的
I know I probably should have said something to you.
我只是真的很忙 忙着规划
I've just been really busy and planning
忙着在最后一刻把所有事都准备好
and getting everything together at the last minute
准备食物啊 花啊 蜜月啊...
with the food, the flowers, the honeymoon...
我们会去巴黎 那应该会很有趣
We're going to Paris, which should be really fun.
我又在闲扯了 是吧?
I'm rambling, aren't I?
- 对 我又在闲扯了 - 一点点
- Yep, I am. - Ah, just a little.
好吧...
Yeah...
总之 我们不想再等了
Anyway, we just didn't want to wait anymore.
当你觉得是时候了 就是时候了
I guess when you know, you know.
那祝贺你 我想这一切都会很棒的
Well, congratulations. I think it's all gonna be great.
谢谢你 基利安
Thank you, Killian.
好吧 我先出去了
Okay, I will see you out there.
如果我是你 我会先换掉衣服
Oh, but I'd get changed first if I were you.
好
Yeah.
艾米 我是达什
Amy, it's Dash.
听着 我又来地下墓穴了 那些枝毒都不见了
Listen, I'm down in the catacombs again, and those branches are gone,
现在这又有一种奇怪的液态金属
but there's a strange liquid metal here now.
你三点左右能来这里见我吗?
You want to meet me here around, say, 3:00
你可以看看这里的情况给我点专业意见
so you can take a look at this and give me your expert opinion?
好的 谢谢
All right, thanks.
我一直在找你呢
I've been looking for you.
我现在有点忙
I'm a little busy right now.
这里没人啊
There's no one even here.
就给我一分钟 我保证你会喜欢的
Just give me a minute. I promise you'll like it.
看
Look.
我已经给你看过了地图 但这还有更多
So I showed you the map already, but there's more,
多得多
a lot more.
我爸的日记巨多
My father had tons of these diaries.
他每月都会写完一本
He filled one up every month.
这么多史料 你找到了我的弱点
So much history. You've found my weak spot.
越往后看就越神秘
They get somewhat more cryptic as it goes on.
到结尾的时候他都开始失控了
He started losing it towards the end.
这是他去世前写的那本
That's the one he was keeping write before he died.
看看最后几页
Check out the last few pages.
"英德尚格波丽"?
"A parching imbued"?
这是什么意思?
What does that mean?
我想这是密码 我感觉这好像和仙宫有关联
I think it's a code. I feel like it's connected to Asgard somehow,
我需要你帮我弄明白它 英格丽德
but I need your help to figure it out, Ingrid.
让我们创造历史吧 我们可以一起做这事
Let's make history. We can do this together.
为什么是我?
Why me?
因为你是女巫
Because you're a witch.
我不是女巫
I'm not a witch.
这里举行慈善活动时我见过你
I saw you at the charity event right here.
有个家伙开始对你毛手毛脚
That guy started getting rough with you.
你说了些拉丁语 他的手指就断了
You said some words in Latin. His fingers just broke.
这就是你的证据吗? 想象力真丰富啊
That is your evidence? You have a very vivid imagination.
如果我错了 你为什么逃跑呢?
If I'm wrong, then why are you running away?
我有工作要做!
I have work to do!
嘿 过来
Hey. Come here.
好了 看看这
Okay, check this out.
就在这
Right here.
明天我们就从这开始我们的新生活了
This is where we start our new life tomorrow.
真的要发生了 感觉好不真实
It just feels so surreal that it's actually happening.
是否感觉我向你求婚是很久之前的事了
Does feel like forever ago when I asked you to marry me.
我可以坦白一下吗?
Can I make a confession?
我从未想过要结婚
I never wanted to get married.
什么?
What?
我总觉得婚姻很... 传统
I just always thought marriage was too... conventional
还很无聊 很平常
and boring and normal.
是人生中任何冒险活动的终结
The end of any adventure in life.
- 我应该担心吗? - 直到我遇见你
- Should I be getting worried? - Until I met you.
然后我意识到婚姻不仅仅是篱笆小院和小货车
And I realized that marriage is more than a picket fence and a minivan.
它是和你爱的人分享你的生活
It's about sharing your life with someone you love.
你知道吗 作为一个环游过世界的人
You know, as someone who's been all over the world,
我... 我实话说
I... I can honestly say,
这一切 当下的这一切...
this, this right here...
这次探险是我最期待的
this is the adventure I'm most looking forward to.
我也是
Me, too.
哟 这不是维克托嘛
Well, well, well, if it isn't Victor.
- 温迪...? - 正是在下
- Wendy...? - In the flesh.
我得多久没见过你了...
Wow. I haven't seen you in...
很久了 别算了
A long time. Let's not put a number on it.
你来这做什么呢 温迪?
So what are you doing here, Wendy?
我以为波尚家族的人都恨我
I thought all the Beauchamps officially hated me.
我们确实恨你 但我们也需要你的帮助
We do officially hate you, but we also need your help.
弗雷娅需要你的帮助
Well, Freya needs your help.
你还记得弗雷娅是谁吧?
You do remember who Freya is, right?
等下 乔安娜知道你在这吗?
Wait. Does Joanna know you're here?
我们讨论过这事
We discussed it.
那 出了什么事?
So, what's the problem?
弗雷娅失去了她的法力
Freya's lost her powers.
确切地说 某人夺走了它们
Well, to be more precise, somebody's taken them,
我们尝试了一切我们能想到的 除了一件事
and we've tried everything we can think of except one thing.
- 不 不 不 绝对不行 - 让我讲完
- No. No. No. Absolutely not. - Let me finish.
我已经很久不行医了也很久没做那种事了
Look, I haven't practiced medicine or done that kind of thing in a long time.
我现在是教授 我更喜欢历史和学术活动
I'm a professor now. I'm more into history, academics.
但我肯定你还记得怎么做
But I'm sure you can remember how to do it.
你知道你在要求什么 对吗?
You do know what you're asking, right?
如果这不重要 我就不会来这儿了
I wouldn't be here if it wasn't important.
还有 这里面还有更多的故事 就给我五分钟
Plus, there is way more to the story. Just give me five minutes.
很快了...
Soon...
妈咪嘛咪哄
Reformabit verum.
达什 嘿 我... 我来得有点早了...
Dash, hey. I, uh... I got here a little early...
我在这等着你
I'll just see you when you get here.
妈咪嘛咪哄
Veniat ad me metalli.
加德纳夫人?
Mrs. Gardiner?
艾米 你怎么来了?
Amy. What are you doing here?
达什约了我在这见面
I'm supposed to be meeting Dash.
我真心觉得你不该碰那东西
I really don't think you should touch that.
为什么? 你觉得这很危险吗?
Why? Do you think it's dangerous?
很有可能 我们还不知道那是什么
It might be. We don't know what it is.
达什和我一直在调查 但...
Dash and I have been investigating, but...
事实上 它是种毒药
Actually, it's a poison,
它是从另一个世界渗透穿墙而来的
and it's seeping through the wall from another world.
有这个可能
That's certainly a theory.
这是个事实 亲爱的
It's a fact, dear.
好在 它对凡人是致命的
Good thing, it's lethal to mortals.
艾米?
Amy?
妈妈 天呐 你吓我一跳 你怎么来了?
Mom. Oh, my God, you scared me. What are you doing here?
我不是你的母亲
I'm not your mother.
妈咪嘛咪哄
Mitte.
天呐 请别这样
Oh, God, please. Don't.
- 救命! 不! - 闭... 嘴
- Help! No! - Shut... up.
真漂亮
So pretty.
天呐
Oh, my God.
帮我给你母亲带个话儿
Give your mother a message from me.
妈咪嘛咪哄
Per mortem argenteum.
弗雷娅?
Freya?
妈妈 假冒者刚来过酒吧
Mom. The shifter was just here at the bar.
- 你没事吧? - 嗯 我没事
- Are you okay? - Yeah, I'm all right.
她刚走 我还可以看到她 她到第四街道去了
She just left, though. I can see her. She's headed down Fourth Street.
待在弯曲手肘
Stay at the Bent Elbow.
那 你怎么看? 你能做吗?
So, what do you think? Can you do it?
能 不过很危险
Yes, but it's dangerous,
我们需要乔安娜参与才能完成
and we need Joanna to pull it off.
没有她的话能完成吗?
Ooh. Um, can we do it without her?
这样就容易多了 我能代替她吗?
I mean, it would be so much easier. Can I do it for her?
不 必须得是乔安...
No, it has to be Joann...
温迪?
Wendy?
- 怎么? - 你跟我说她知道我要来
- What? - You told me she knew I was coming.
不 我没说 我说我们讨论过了
No, I didn't. I said that we discussed it.
讨论的结果是她不让我找你
And the discussion ended with her telling me not to find you.
- 她什么时候回来? - 我不知道
- When is she getting back? - I don't know.
不如你在我屋子里等等吧
But it might be a good idea for you to wait in my room.
我可能需要慢慢告诉她 不 等等!
I might need to break it to her gently. No, wait! Oh.
- 这根本不是个好主意 - 你不能走
- This is not a good idea at all. - You can't leave.
你向我保证过 我们说好了的
You made me a promise. We had a deal.
现在到我屋里去!
Now go to my room!
迈克 我们要关门了 你得走了
Mike. We're closed. You need to leave.
"英德尚格波丽." 我知道这是什么意思
"A parching imbued." I know what it means.
- 我不关心 - 这是字母易位词
- I don't care. - It's an anagram.
你该走了
It's time for you to leave.
它的意思是"英格丽德・波尚"
It means "Ingrid Beauchamp."
我不知道你在说什么 我也不想知道
I don't know what you're talking about, and I don't want to know.
要是你改变"英德尚格波丽"的字母顺序
If you rearrange the letters of "A Parching Imbued,"
就可以拼出你的名字... 英格丽德・波尚
it spells your name... Ingrid Beauchamp.
我跟你说了 我们要关门了 你得马上离开
I told you. We are closed. You need to leave right now.
问题是 在我父亲的日记里
Question is, why would my father
为什么会有你名字的字母易位词呢?
have an anagram of your name in his diary?
- 好了 我要叫警察了 - 不 你不会的
- Okay, I'm gonna call the police. - No, you're not.
上次在图书馆被我赶走的那个家伙
What did you say happened to the last guy
还记得他怎么样了...
who cornered me in the library...
他的手指怎么样了吗?
something about broken fingers?
一点儿不差 因为你用咒语做到的
Exactly, 'cause you broke it with a spell,
因为你就是个女巫
because you are a witch.
好了 你在骚扰我 我要叫警察了
Okay. Now you're harassing me. I'm calling the police.
要是你承认事实 我们就可以继续了
If you just admit the truth, we can move on.
- 我不是女巫! - 我知道你在隐藏秘密
- I am not a witch! - I know you're sworn to secrecy.
我父亲连续几年研究你们的文化 我知道密码
My father studied your culture for years. I know about the code.
根本没有密码! 我不知道你在说什么
There is no code! I don't know what you're talking about.
好吧
Fine.
我来证明一下
I'll prove it.
天哪!
Oh, my God!
迈克!
Mike!
我觉得特别无助 太恐怖了
I just felt completely defenseless. It was awful.
然后她告诉我给你捎个信
And then she told me to give you a message.
妈咪嘛咪哄?
Per mortem argenteum?
什么? 这是什么意思?
What? What does that mean?
意思是我们得恢复你的能力
It means we need to get your powers back.
可是你和温迪都说了这是不可能的啊
But you and Wendy both said there was no way.
还有一种可能
Mm, there's still one possibility.
这太疯狂了! 你为什么要这么做?!
This is insane! Why are you doing this?!
你得马上把我治好 要不我就会流血致死了
You need to heal me right now, or I'm gonna bleed to death.
我知道你能做到...
I know you can do it...
每个女巫都有疗伤的能力
every witch has healing power.
我不会治好你 你才不关心你的死活
I'm not healing you. I don't care if you die.
你应该不想向警察解释这些吧
I don't think you want to explain this to the police.
你能解释啊! 我要打911!
You can explain it! I'll just call 911!
医务人员到这里之前我就死了
I'll be dead before the paramedics get here.
求你... 治好我吧
Just... heal me.
- 你疯了 你知道吗? - 我已经决定了
- You are insane, do you know that? - I'm determined.
我到这里来是找去仙宫的路
I came here to find the way to Asgard,
来完成我父亲的工作
to finish my father's life work.
不过没有你我做不到
But I can't do it without you.
我需要你 英格丽德
I need you, Ingrid.
求你了 不要让我在这里死掉
Please, don't let me die here.
我以前从没有治疗过别人
I've never even healed anyone before.
我不确定这有没有用
I'm not sure if this will work.
至少 我们在进步了...
We're making some progress, at least...
- 你已经承认了 - 我没承认
- You're admitting something. - I admit nothing.
妈咪嘛咪哄
Haec vulnera sanaret lunaticus est scriptor.
医治 医治 医治 医治 医治 医治
Sana, sana, sana. Sana, sana, sana.
医治 医治 医治
Sana, sana, sana.
这... 太不可思议了
That... was incredible.
去死吧
Go to hell.
嘿
Hey.
弗雷娅被假冒者攻击了
Freya got attacked by the shifter.
什么?! 你还好吗?
What?! Are you okay?
嗯 我现在好了
Yeah, I'm okay now.
她给我带了个话 妈咪嘛咪哄
She sent me a message. Per mortem argenteum.
不是吧
No.
好吧 这是什么意思? 肯定不是好事
Okay, what does this mean? It can't be good.
我只认识一个意思是"死亡"的词
The only word I understand there means "death."
我想我们需要叫维克托过来
I think we need to call Victor.
对 完全同意
Yeah. I totally agree.
维克托!
Victor!
搞什么?
What the hell?
想想我们节省了多少时间吧
Just think of all the time we just saved.
谁是维克托?
Who is Victor?
真的是你
It's really you.
妈妈 这是谁?
Mom, who is this?
他是你父亲
He's your father.
嘿 对不起
Hey. I'm sorry.
我知道这有点突然
I'm sure that really felt like an ambush.
我发誓我不知道他在这儿
I swear I did not know that he was here.
那就是我父亲
That's my father in there.
我父亲... 我曾经见过的父亲
My father... who I've never met,
在我出生前就离开的父亲... 就在这里
who left before I was born... is here.
他就在我家厨房
He's in my kitchen.
我本不想让你们以这种方式见面
I didn't want you to meet him like this.
弗雷娅?
Freya?
- 我能跟你聊聊吗? - 不用了 她没事
- Can I talk to you? - Nah, she's fine.
不 妈妈 没事的 给我们点时间吧 好吗?
No, Mom, it's okay. Just give us a second, okay?
- 她保护意识很强 - 她一直都这样
- She's protective. - She always was.
听着 我知道你在想什么
Look, I know what you're thinking.
我觉得你不知道 你根本就不了解我
I don't think you do. You don't even know me.
我不知道... 我现在什么感觉
I have no idea... How I'm feeling right now.
我一辈子都在想你是谁 你在哪里
My whole life I've wondered who you were, where you were,
然后你就突然
and now you just show up,
在我婚礼的前一天出现在我家
in my house, the day before my wedding.
我从来不会掌握时机
Timing was never my thing.
对
Yeah.
可我已经来了 弗雷娅 我...
Look, but I'm here now, Freya, and I...
我想帮助你
I'd like to help you.
要是你愿意的话
If you'll let me.
你知道这个咒语是很痛苦的
You need to know this spell can be very painful.
你会感觉你的身体内部被扭曲了
Your body will feel like it's being twisted from within.
到底是什么?
And what is it, exactly?
就像一次输血
It's like a transfusion.
需要你的父母都给你他们的血
It requires both parents to give you their blood.
不过任何跟血有关的医学咒语都很危险
But any medical spell that mixes blood is dangerous.
而这个甚至更冒险
And this one is even more risky, because of
因为它得很强烈才能起作用
how strong it needs to be in order for it to work.
没有其他的办法了吗?
And there's no other way to do it?
我真的希望有
I really hoped there was,
不过维克托和我考虑过其他所有可能性
but Victor and I have looked at every other possibility
这是唯一可行的办法
and this is the only one that remains.
我看过这个咒语起作用 所以这是合理的
I've seen this spell work. So it is possible.
合理也很危险
But possible and dangerous,
所以如果你有其他的方案...
so if you are having second thoughts...
不 就这么办吧
No. I'm doing it.
裂痕
Lacera.
融合
Concorporo.
没关系 她没事的 乔安娜
No, she's fine, Joanna.
我让你停你再停 好吗?
Just don't let go until I tell you, okay?
- 天哪... - 弗雷娅...
- Oh... oh, God... - Freya...
这只是过程的一部分 没事的
This is just part of the process. It's okay.
天哪 快停下!
Oh, God, make it stop!
维克托 有问题 我能感觉出来
Victor, something's wrong; I can feel it.
不 我们快完成了 她没事的
No. We're almost there. She's fine.
没事 我以前碰到过这种情况
It's okay, I've seen this before.
我们的血液在压制她自己的血液 没事的
Our blood is overpowering her own. It's okay.
- 爸爸! - 有问题!
- Daddy! - Something not right!
- 她快不行了! - 救命啊!
- She's slipping away! - Oh, God!
- 求求你们停下! - 马上就好
- Please make it stop! - Just wait.
- 马上好... - 够了 维克托!
- Just wait... - Let go, Victor!
该死的 乔安娜! 只要...
Damn it, Joanna! Just...
怎么了? 成功了吗?
What happened? Did it work?
弗雷娅 很抱歉
Freya, I am so sorry.
我只是 我不能... 我不能冒这个险
I just, I couldn't... I couldn't risk it.
太危险了
It was too dangerous,
只要你活着
and I would rather have you alive
我宁愿你没有魔法也不希望...
with no powers than...
弗雷娅 等等
Freya, please wait.
- 嗨 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
- 难熬的一天 - 你根本想不到
- Ugh. Rough day. - You have no idea.
- 我觉得我要赢了 - 我打赌你赢不了
- I think I'm gonna win. - I bet you don't.
我今天在图书馆和迈克一起
I had the most intense situation
出了特别棘手的状况
at the library today with this guy, Mike...
我今天见到我们的爸爸了
I met our father today.
- 什么? - 我见到他了
- What? - I met him.
他还活着
He's real.
他是哥伦比亚大学的历史教授
He's a history professor at Columbia.
你和他蛮像的
He looks like you.
那很不错
Well, good for him.
你这是什么意思?
What does that mean?
我是说我一点都不想见他
It means I have no interest in meeting him.
永远都不想见 他离开了我们 弗雷娅
Ever. He left us, Freya,
从没回来过
and never came back.
但你一点都不好奇吗?
But aren't you just a little bit curious?
你从没想过他长什么样?
Haven't you always wondered what he was like?
当然有过
Sure.
很久很久以前
A long time ago.
我曾经幻想有一天放学回家
I used to fantasize about coming home from school one day,
他会坐在门口
and he would be sitting on the front porch
拿着书 玩具和礼物
with books and presents and toys,
然后... 他会拥抱我
and... he would hug me
然后我们一起吃冰淇淋
and we would eat ice cream together
还熬夜看电影
and stay up late watching movies.
但是我从小到大都没享受过这种生活
But then I outgrew all of that.
一件事都没有
All of it.
他不想认识我们 弗雷娅 我也不想认识他
He didn't want to know us, Freya. I don't want to know him.
好吧 但我想了解他
Well, I'd like to get to know him.
行吧 那... 那是你的决定
Okay. Well, that's... that's your decision.
- 好吧 我们别谈这个了 - 嗯 好主意
- Okay, let's not talk about this. - Yeah. Good reveal.
告诉我你和迈克之间发生了什么
Tell me about what happened with Mike.
没什么的... 这一点都不重要
No, it's not... it's not that important.
嗨 弗雷娅 你准备度蜜月了
Hey, Freya, between you going on your honeymoon
基利安也要离开
and Killand taking off,
我需要一些人手来这里帮忙
I'm gonna need some help around here.
要是你知道有人...
So if you know anybody...
等等 不好意思...
Wait, I'm sorry...
你说什么 基利安要走?
What do you mean, Killian's taking off?
- 他没告诉你吗? - 没有
- He didn't tell you? - No.
基利安明天就走 坐船去哥斯达黎加
Killian's leaving tomorrow. Sailing to Costa Rica.
所以... 我希望你早点回来
So... I hope you'll be back soon.
喂
Hey.
也许这是最好的结局
Maybe it's for the best.
你和达什可以重新开始
I mean, you and Dash, you get a clean start.
- 是啊 - 是的
- Yeah. - Yeah.
我们得去彩排晚宴了
We have a rehearsal dinner to get to.
好的
Okay.
谢谢你
Thank you.
来一杯
Drink up.
谢谢
Oh. Oh, thank you.
你们也来一杯吧
Here you go, guys.
好
Great.
有东西开始在布上显现出来了
Something's beginning to form on the canvas.
我还没法让它显现出来
I can't quite make it out yet,
但好像马上就出现了
but it looks like it's coming soon.
大家都准备好了吗?
Are we all ready here?
是 每个人都有一杯
Yep. Everyone has a glass.
好的 大家都有香槟了 我们来敬酒吧
All right, now that everybody's got champagne, let's have a toast.
当然了 我最喜欢了
Oh, of course. I'd love to.
我还真是一点也不惊讶呢
Why am I not surprised?
放松... 就说几句
Oh, relax... it's just a few words.
好了...
Well...
今天我们欢聚一堂
It's taken a series of fortunate events to bring us all here today.
当我第一次发现东区和费尔黑文 我就知道
When I first discovered East End and Fair Haven, I knew this was the place
这是我一直寻找的地方
that I'd always been searching for.
当达什遇见了弗雷娅
And then when Dash met Freya,
我不禁想 " 我怎么可以这么幸运? "
I thought, "Could I really be so lucky?"
因为我知道我不仅有了弗雷娅这个儿媳妇
Because I knew I wasn't just getting Freya,
我还结识了整个波尚家族
I was getting all the Beauchamps.
真是一份极好的礼物
What a gift.
来让我们举杯...
So raise a glass...
祝福你们有一个让所有人难忘的婚礼
To a wedding no one will ever forget.
- 干杯 - 干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
干杯
Cheers.
太棒了 好了 我来倒酒
That's great. Yeah. I'm just gonna refill them.
好了 大家放松一下好好玩吧
Well, everybody relax and enjoy yourselves.
宴会马上就好
Dinner'll be ready soon.
怎么样?
Well?
唾液没血液那么明显 但也有用
Well, saliva isn't as good as blood, but it's working.
还有呢?
And?
每个人都恢复凡人状态了 包括佩内洛普
Everybody's coming back mortal, even Penelope.
我会继续确认的
I'll keep checking.
好的 这我就放心了
Well, that's a relief.
温迪 炉子没开火!
Wendy, the oven isn't on!
你可是个女巫诶
You're a witch.
加热
Oh. Calor.
你看过那个画了吗?
Have you checked the painting?
是啊 我为什么不看看画呢?
Why don't I check the painting? Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
你来这里干什么?
What are you doing here?
我叫他回来的
I asked him to come back.
你在想什么呢 弗雷娅?
What were you thinking, Freya?
我想和我的父亲在一起
I was thinking I wanted to spend time with my father.
维克托 我想你该离开
Victor, I think you should leave.
我觉得弗雷娅的彩排晚宴
I just don't think that Freya's rehearsal dinner
不是个修补关系的好时间
is the right time to reconnect.
拜托? 就像你说的 这是我的彩排晚宴
Hello? Like you said, it's my rehearsal dinner.
要是我想他在这里 他就可以在这里
If I want him to stay, he can stay.
我要辩解一下 乔安娜
In my defense, Joanna,
我今天过来 不是仅仅露个面
I was brought here today. I didn't just show up.
既然我来了 我至少应该和她们说说话
But now that I'm here, I should at least be able to speak to them.
她们也是我的孩子
They're my children, too.
除非她们不会跟你说话
Not if they don't want to speak to you.
- 我 我想 - 为什么?
- l, I would like to speak to him. - Why?
你去哪里了? 我指的不止是这一世
Where have you been? And I don't just mean in this life.
我看过无数过去的照片...一个都没有你
I've seen tons of pictures from the past... you're not in any of them.
- 英格丽德 我能解释的 - 对不起
- Ingrid, I can explain. - I'm sorry.
我不想听你的解释
I don't want to hear your explanations.
嘿 各位 只有我和加德纳一家在
Hey, guys. It's getting kind of weird back there
显得有点奇怪呢
with just me and the Gardiners.
嘿 你回来了
Oh, hey. You're back.
我要去上菜了
I have to get dinner on the table.
我知道你来不是你自己的意思
I know it wasn't your idea to come here.
很抱歉 妈妈和英格丽德那样对你
I'm sorry for the way Mom and Ingrid are being.
没事的 弗雷娅
It's okay, Freya.
她们有她们的原因
They have their reasons.
如果我是她们 也不会想跟我说话了
If I were them, I wouldn't talk to me either.
我能... 给你看样东西吗?
Hey. Can I... show you something?
我知道我离开了 但是我... 我有努力
I know I've been gone but I... I do keep up.
尽我所能
As best I can.
我不理解
I don't understand.
你离开了我们
You left us.
但我离开并不是因为不爱你
Uh... but I didn't leave because I didn't love you.
弗雷娅 亲爱的 你要错过晚饭了
Freya, sweetie, you're missing your dinner.
我想... 单独跟你爸爸谈谈
And I'd like to... talk to your father alone.
乔安娜 我没有...
Look, Joanna, I don't...
不 听我说
No, just listen.
弗雷娅不需要再接近你然后再次被抛弃
Freya does not need to get close to you only to be abandoned again.
我没有抛弃任何人
I did not abandon anyone.
你就是这样跟她们说的吗?
Is that what you told them?
我还能怎么说呢?
Well, what should I have told them?
- 我现在不能这么做 - 乔安娜...
- I can't do this now. - Joanna...
宝贝
Babe.
你好吗?
You okay?
很好 不好意思 我只是在屋里有点压抑
Yeah. Sorry. It's just a little overwhelming in there.
我想象的到
I can imagine.
我只想透透气
I just needed to get outside.
我们去走走吧?
Why don't we go somewhere?
什么意思?
What do you mean?
好啦 我们走吧 就... 你和我
Come on. Let's go. Just... you and me.
我们一起去冒险吧
Let's start our adventure together.
- 一切都还好吗? - 不 不好
- Is everything okay? - No. Not really.
一点都不好
Not at all.
我知道你爸爸在这儿...
I know your dad being here...
我没心情听那个人的借口
I'm not in the mood for this man's excuses.
你知道吗?
You know?
他错过了他的机会
He missed his chance.
温迪
Wendy.
我能单独跟英格丽德谈谈吗?
Can I speak to Ingrid alone, please?
英格丽德...
Ingrid...
她不会那么容易原谅你 相信我
Yeah. That one doesn't forgive so easy. Take it from me.
在海边的时候 我总会感觉好点
I always feel better when I'm by the ocean.
海那么广阔 让我的问题看起来很渺小
It's so big. It makes my problems feel small.
应该说是我们的问题
Well, now they're our problems.
要是你没办法改变的事呢?
What if it's something you can't fix?
还没有这样的事
No such thing.
- 我是个医生 - 我是认真的
- I'm a doctor. - I'm serious.
我是说 看看我的爸妈
I mean, look at my parents.
他们深爱着彼此 我看的出来
They loved each other. I know they did.
但是... 那还不够 他们还是会分开
But... it's not always enough. It can still fall apart.
不论你多么爱一个人 他们还是会离开的
No matter how much you love someone, they can still walk away.
我不会离开你的 永远不会
I won't walk away from you. Ever.
我打赌我爸妈也跟彼此说过这样的话
I bet my parents told each other the same thing.
他们不能在一起不代表我们也一定会分开
Just because it didn't work for them doesn't mean that it won't for us.
这是... 你必须做的选择
It's... a choice you have to make,
就是你哪儿也不会去
that you're not going anywhere.
即使这个选择很难 尤其是确实很难的时候
Even when it gets hard. Especially when it gets hard.
我保证我每天都会做出这样的选择
I promise you I will make that choice every day.
我和你对抗整个世界
It's you and me against the world.
好吗?
Deal?
好
Deal.
该把你送回家了
We should probably get you home soon.
对啊 该回去了
Yeah. Probably should.
我得说我想念你的聚会了
I got to say I missed your... your parties.
你做的饭 还有...
And your cooking. And, uh...
还有你
And you.
乔安娜 无论如何
Joanna, for what it's worth,
你都一个人做了一件...
you know, you've done a...
非常棒的事
Pretty great job on your own.
这所有的一切
With everything.
我无法想象你经历了多少困难
I can't imagine how hard it must've been on you.
谢谢你
So thank you.
谢谢你照顾好我们的女儿
Thank you for taking such good care of our girls.
不客气 谢谢你能这么说 维克托
You're welcome. Thank you for saying that, Victor.
你或许不相信我 但是我仍然想你
You probably don't believe me, but I... I still think about you.
每天
Every day.
但是你一直知道我在哪儿 我们在哪儿
And yet you've always known where I am. Where all of us are.
你知道我从来没有停止过爱你
You know I never stopped loving you.
那不是我们分开的原因
That wasn't what drove us apart.
我试着用几个轮回的时间来忘记你
I've tried for centuries to forget you.
但那没用
It doesn't work.
当我见到你 我仍然...
When I see you, I still...
维克托...
Victor...
英格丽德
Ingrid.
迈克 你怎么找到我的?
Mike, how did you find me here?
我是个探索者 记得吗?
I'm an explorer, remember?
我查了一下电话簿
I explored a phone book.
你不能就这么出现在我家 你有什么事?
You can't just show up at my house. Why are you here?
有件事我需要跟你说
There's something I need to talk to you about.
我知道通往仙宫的门在哪儿
I know where the door to Asgard is.
我还知道怎么通过那道门
And I know how to get through.
没办法过去的
There's no way through.
只有一把钥匙 但是被毁了
There was only one key, and it was destroyed.
那个巨蛇座吗?
The serpens clavem?
是的 我还有其他办法 英格丽德
Yeah, I know some things, too, Ingrid.
还有第二把钥匙 这就是我想告诉你的
There's a second key. This is what I've been trying to tell you.
- 它在哪儿? - 不是哪儿 而是谁
- Where is it? - Not where. It's who.
是你 英格丽德
It's you, Ingrid.
"英德尚格波丽"就是另一把钥匙
"A parching imbued" is the other key.
你就是那把钥匙 你要帮我打开它
You're the other key. And you're gonna help me open it.
这跟我想的一样吗?
Is that what I think it is?
这个镇子唯一的隧道就是
The only tunnels in this town
费尔黑文下面的地下墓穴
are the catacombs under Fair Haven.
我想不出来还会是什么
I don't know what else it could be.
我以为它是要给我们看假冒者是谁
Well, I thought it was supposed to show us who the shifter is.
本来是的
It was.
我不知道这是什么意思
I don't know what this means.
那我们就要想办法弄明白
Well, we need to figure it out.
弗雷娅明天要在那里结婚
Freya's getting married there tomorrow.
我终于要杀了她了 爸爸
I'm finally going to kill her, Father.
然后我就回家
And then I'm coming home.
你来干什么?
What are you doing here?
我来跟你说再见
I couldn't leave without saying good-bye.
我爱上你了
I'm in love with you.
- 什么? - 跟我走
- What? - Come with me.
我们今晚就可以离开
We can leave tonight.
等等 你不能这么想
Wait. Y... You need to stop.
我们属于彼此 你知道的
We belong together. You know we do.
这太疯狂了 我明天要跟达什结婚了
This is crazy. I am marrying Dash tomorrow.
你不能嫁给达什 你只会被他占有
You can't marry Dash. You'll just become another one of his possessions.
我们之间是不会变成那样的
It wouldn't be like that with us.
没有什么"我们" 基利安
There is no "us," Killian.
在遇见我之前你梦到我了
You dreamt about me before you met me.
我也梦到你了
I dreamt about you, too.
我都不敢相信你是真实存在的
I didn't even think you existed
直到我在订婚晚会上遇见你
until I met you at that engagement party.
我的整个人生 我以为我一直在逃避
My whole life, I thought I was running away
所有人 所有事
from everyone, everything.
但是现在我知道...
But now I know I was...
这一切都是为了遇见你
Just running toward you.
我爱你 在遇见你之前就爱上你了
I love you. I loved you even before I met you.
你嫁给他 会毁了你的
You marry him, it'll destroy you.